# business_management_quiz.py

questions = [
    {
        "question": "What is the primary goal of order management?",
        "options": ["a. To increase sales revenue", "b. To improve customer satisfaction",
                    "c. To streamline order processing and fulfillment", "d. To reduce inventory costs"],
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which order management process involves verifying customer information?",
        "options": ["a. Order receipt", "b. Order processing", "c. Order fulfillment", "d. Order verification"],
        "answer": "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of order tracking?",
        "options": ["a. To monitor inventory levels", "b. To track customer interactions",
                    "c. To ensure timely delivery of orders", "d. To analyze sales trends"],
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the primary role of a sales representative?",
        "options": ["a. To provide customer support", "b. To manage inventory levels",
                    "c. To generate sales revenue", "d. To develop marketing campaigns"],
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a key skill for a sales representative?",
        "options": ["a. Technical knowledge", "b. Communication skills", "c. Product knowledge", "d. All of the above"],
        "answer": "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sales strategy involves building relationships with customers?",
        "options": ["a. Transactional selling", "b. Consultative selling", "c. Solution selling", "d. Account management"],
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the primary goal of customer service?",
        "options": ["a. To increase sales revenue", "b. To reduce customer complaints",
                    "c. To improve customer satisfaction", "d. To provide product information"],
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which customer service channel is most commonly used?",
        "options": ["a. Phone", "b. Email", "c. Live chat", "d. Social media"],
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the primary goal of fulfillment management?",
        "options": ["a. To improve customer satisfaction", "b. To reduce shipping costs",
                    "c. To increase inventory levels", "d. To streamline order processing"],
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a key performance indicator (KPI) for fulfillment management?",
        "options": ["a. Order fulfillment rate", "b. Shipping accuracy rate",
                    "c. Inventory turnover rate", "d. Return rate"],
        "answer": "a"
    }
]
